In this video, we're going to continue our discussion of type checking and cool with
在这段视频中，我们将继续讨论类型检查，并通过
the rules for type checking methods and method calls. So here's the situation, we
类型检查方法和方法调用的规则。所以情况是这样的，我们
want to type check a method call, let's say that we have a dispatch on some
我想键入check a方法调用，假设我们在一些
expression easier, and we're calling some method named F, and we have some arguments
表达式更简单，我们调用一些名为F的方法，我们有一些参数
E one through E N. Well, so clearly we're gonna type check E zero, it's gonna have
从E 1到E N，很明显我们要输入检查E 0，它会有
some type E zero, and similarly we're gonna type check all of the arguments and
一些类型为E的零，类似地，我们将键入check所有参数，然后
they're gonna have some types, and then the question is, what is the return type
它们会有一些类型，然后问题是，返回类型是什么
of this method call, what value, what kind of value do we get back after we call this
在调用这个方法之后，我们会得到什么值，会得到什么样的值
method? And as you can probably see we're in a very similar situation here that we
方法呢？正如你可能看到的，我们在这里的情况非常相似，我们
were in before when we were typing check the variable reference. We have this name
都在前面，当我们键入check变量引用时。我们有这个名字
F and we don't know anything about what it does, we don't know the behavior of F is
我们对它的作用一无所知，我们不知道F的行为
unless we have some information about F's behavior, we can't really say what kind of
除非我们有一些关于F的行为的信息，否则我们真的不能说是哪种
value it is going to return. An added wrinkle in cool is that method object
它将返回的价值。在Cooler中增加了一条皱纹，那就是方法对象
identifiers live in different name spaces. That is, it is possible in the same scope
标识符位于不同的名称空间中。也就是说，在相同的范围内是可能的
to have a method called foo and also an object called foo and we won't get them
有一个名为foo的方法，还有一个名为foo的对象，但是我们不会得到它们
confused. They are different enough and used differently enough in the language
很困惑。它们有很大的不同，在语言中的用法也有很大的不同
that we can always tell when we're talking about the object foo and when we're
当我们谈论物体Foo的时候，我们总是可以分辨出，当我们
talking about the method foo. But what this means in effect is that there's two
说到方法foo。但这实际上意味着有两个
different environments. One for objects and one for methods and so in the type
不同的环境。一个用于对象，另一个用于类型中的方法，依此类推
rules, this is going to be reflected by having a separate mapping a separate
规则，这将通过将单独的映射设置为单独的
method environment that's going to record the signature of each of the methods. And
将记录每个方法的签名的方法环境。和
a signature, as is a standard name that you'll probably hear used in other
签名，因为它是您可能在其他应用程序中听到的标准名称
contexts, but the signature of a function is just its input and output types. And so
上下文，但是函数的签名仅仅是它的输入和输出类型。因此，
this table, m, is gonna take the name of a class. It's gonna take the name of a
这张桌子，m，将以班级的名字命名。它将以一个
method in that class and is just gonna tell us what are the argument types of the
方法，并且只会告诉我们
methods. So all but the last type in the list here is one of the arguing types of
方法。因此，除了列表中的最后一种类型之外，这里的所有类型都是
the method and then the last type is the result type. That's the type of the return
方法，然后最后一个类型是结果类型。这就是退货的类型
value. So the way we are going to write the method signature is just as a tutor or
价值。因此，我们编写方法签名的方式只是作为一个导师或
a list of types, the first, all but the last one taken together are the, are the
类型列表，第一个，除最后一个之外的所有类型都是，是
types of the arguments in order. And then the very last one is the type of the
按顺序排列的参数类型。最后一个问题是
result And so an entry like this in our method, environment just means that f has
结果，所以在我们的方法中，像这样的条目，环境只是意味着f具有
a signature that looks like this. It takes in arguments, with the respective types
一个看起来像这样的签名。它接受具有各自类型的参数
and it returns something of type t n plus one. So with the method environment added
它返回的是tn加1类型的东西。所以添加了方法环境之后
to our rules, now we can write a rule for dispatch. So notice, first of all, that we
按照我们的规则，现在我们可以写一条规则来派遣了。所以请注意，首先，我们
have these two mappings, one for object identifiers and one for method names on
有这两个映射，一个用于对象标识符，另一个用于方法名
the left hand side of the turnstile. We have to propagate that method environment
旋转栅门的左手边。我们必须传播该方法环境
through all the typing for the sub expressions and for the case of method
通过对子表达式和方法的所有类型进行
dispatch, we just type The, type of the expression we're dispatching to e zero,
分派，我们只需键入，我们要分派到e0的表达式的类型，
and all of the arguments and get types t one through t n, and then we look up the
以及所有的参数和获取类型t1到tn，然后我们查找
type of f in the class t zero. So, what class are we dispatching to? Well, that's
类t 0中的f的类型。那么，我们要派到哪个班呢？嗯，那是
gonna be to the class of e zero And so where do we look up m in our environment.
将会是e0的班级，那么在我们的环境中，我们应该在哪里查找m呢？
Where there better be a method called F to find in class T0, and it must have some
在类T0中最好有一个名为F的方法来查找，并且它必须有一些
signature with the right number of arguments. And then, the actual arguments
使用正确数量的参数签名。然后，实际的论点是
that we're passing, the E1 through E-N, they're types have to be sub-types of the
我们正在通过的E1到E-N，它们的类型必须是
declared formal parameter. So here, the signature of F. Says that, for example,
声明的形参。在这里，F.的签名是这样说的，例如，
the first argument of f has type t one prime, and so we're going to require that
f的第一个参数的t类型是一个素数，所以我们需要
the type of e one be some type t one such that t one is a sub type of t one prime.
e_1类型是某种类型t_1，使得t_1是t_1素数的子类型。
And similarly for all the other arguments of the method call. And if all of that
对于该方法调用的所有其他参数也是如此。如果所有这些都是
checks out, if that has a signature like this, and all the sub type requirements on
签出，如果它有这样的签名，以及上的所有子类型要求
the actual arguments and the formal arguments match, then we're going to say
实际论点和形式论点相匹配，那么我们就说
that the entire expression. [inaudible] Return something of type t n plus one the
整个表达方式。[听不见]返回类型为t，n加上1的
return type of the method. The typing rule for static dispatch is very similar to the
该方法的返回类型。静电调度的键入规则与
rule for regular dispatch. So recall that, syntactically, the only thing that's
定期派遣的规则。所以请记住，从句法上讲，唯一
different is that the programmer writes the name of the class at which they wish
不同之处在于，程序员可以随心所欲地编写类的名称
to run the, the method. So instead of running the method F as defined in the
要运行，该方法。因此，不是运行方法F，而是运行
class E0, whatever that class happens to be, we're going to run whatever that
类E0，不管这个类是什么，我们都会运行
method F happens to be in some ancestor class of the class of E0. And how is that
方法F恰好在E0类的某个祖先类中。那是怎么回事呢？
expressed in the type rules? Well once again, we type E0 and all of the
是否在类型规则中表示？再一次，我们键入E0和所有
arguments. And now we require that, whatever the type was we discovered for
争论。现在我们要求，无论我们发现的是什么类型
E0, it has to be a sub-type of T. So T has to be an ancestor type in the class
E0，则它必须是T的子类型。因此，T必须是类中的祖先类型
hierarchy of the type of E0. And moreover, that class T had better have a method
E0类型的层次结构。而且，T类最好有一个方法
called F. That has the right number of our units, with the right kind of types, such
叫做F，它有合适数量的单元，有合适的类型，比如
that all the type constraints work out, that the, actual argument types are sub
所有类型约束都起作用，实际的参数类型是子类型
types of the corresponding formal argument types, and then if all of that is true,
类型，然后如果所有这些都为真，
we'll be able to conclude that the entire dispatch expression has a type t n plus
我们将能够得出结论，整个分派表达式的类型为tn+
one which is the return type of the method.
一个是该方法的返回类型。